https://www.fcclouisville.org/privacy-policy-refund

Privacy Policy and Refund Statement
First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests, and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY for the operation of the service, to maintain the quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY Web site.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY does not read any of your private online communications.
First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY, and First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY family of Web sites.
Use of your Personal Information
First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY collects and uses your personal information to operate the First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY Web site and deliver the services you have requested. First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY and its affiliates.
First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.
First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY, in order to determine what First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY, or the public.Use of CookiesThe First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY Web site use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY pages, or register with First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY site or services, a cookie helps First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY features that you customized.You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY services or Web sites you visit.Security of your Personal InformationFirst Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.
First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.Changes to this StatementFirst Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback.
First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY is protecting your information.Contact InformationFirst Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY has not adhered to this Statement, please contact First Christian Church | Disciples of Christ Community in Louisville, KY at bgerard@fcclouisville.org. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
Refund Statement:
Online contributions to the ministry First Christian Church of Louisville are considered to be non-refundable. The refund policy for specific events is determined according to the nature of the event. The event refund policy is posted within the event registration form.
HomeDiscoverServeWorshipSermonsConnectGiveMore
